<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vSphere with Tanzu 101 – Course Introduction</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/</link><description>Recent content in Course Introduction on vSphere with Tanzu 101</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Docs: Tech Preview</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/techpreview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/techpreview/</guid><description>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Please Note: This course is currently in technical preview&lt;/strong> for
additional review and feedback before the course is generally available.
The purpose of the preview is to validate all information in the course
and to receive input on additions on improvements we can make before GA.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Accordingly, please be aware that any technical details in the course
are still under review and may not be fully accurate.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Your feedback is extremely important!&lt;/strong> We really need your feedback
to make this course the best experience we can. Any and all suggestions
are appreciated from small grammar improvements to bigger additions.
Please describe your suggestions with as much detail as possible. If you
would like to discuss directly with the course development team we would
appreciate it!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please &lt;a href="https://github.com/ModernAppsNinja/CourseFeedback/issues/new?assignees=&amp;amp;labels=COU-VT7933&amp;amp;template=COU-VT7933-feedback.md&amp;amp;title=">submit a feedback ticket
here&lt;/a>,
or feel free to reach out to afewell@vmware.com with other feedback or
suggestions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Welcome to the Course</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/welcometothecourse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/welcometothecourse/</guid><description>
&lt;p>This course provides a technical introduction to vSphere with Tanzu.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This course is a community effort, to be able to keep up the material,
we really need your help to report issues, suggest improvements, or help
with the many volunteer opportunities available to support the
community.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you for investing your time!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Please Note:&lt;/strong> This course no longer provides enrollment, testing, badging or any interactive features. If you see any references to these past features, please disregard.&lt;/p>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5V03CSMkm2c" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Docs: Target Audience</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/targetaudience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/targetaudience/</guid><description>
&lt;p>This course is designed for Information Technology Professionals
interested in learning more about VMware vSphere with Tanzu.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please complete the course prerequisites to ensure you are fully prepared to succeed in this course.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Prerequisites</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/prerequisites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/prerequisites/</guid><description>
&lt;p>We recommend taking the &lt;a href="https://lms.modernapps.ninja/courses/course-v1:modernapps+COU-TP6539+Perpetual/course/">Introduction to VMware Tanzu
Portfolio&lt;/a> course
prior to taking the vSphere with Tanzu 101 course.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This course assumes familiarity with Kubernetes and Cloud Native
Technologies. If you are not familiar with these technologies, we
recommend checking out &lt;a href="https://kube.academy/">KubeAcademy&lt;/a> by VMware,
which has a terrific set of free, bite-size video resources on the
basics of containers, Kubernetes and cloud native that are great for
beginners.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Before taking this course, you should also have familiarity with vSphere
administration. If you need additional background in vSphere, we
recommend checking out &lt;a href="https://hol.vmware.com">VMware Hands on Labs&lt;/a>,
which offers a number of vSphere labs and content.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Course Updates and Freshness</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/courseupdatesandfreshness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/docs/courseintroduction/courseupdatesandfreshness/</guid><description>
&lt;p>We make a strong effort to keep the content in this course as current as
possible, however the Tanzu Portfolio is rapidly growing and there may
be times where this course may not include the newest updates. Always
please refer to the official &lt;a href="https://tanzu.vmware.com/tanzu">VMware Tanzu Portfolio
Website&lt;/a> and your VMware account team
for the latest details on products covered in this course. &lt;/p>
&lt;p>As part of our effort to keep this course as up-to-date as possible,
this course is on a continuous update lifecycle. This means that the
course can be updated at any time, and new content and requirements may
be added while you are taking your course. We will make effort to notify
students in advance of any significant updates are made to minimize any
changes to course completion requirements. &lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>You have reached the last page in this section. Please use the left navigation bar and click on the next section.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>