<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ModernApps Ninja New Course Template – Course Introduction</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/</link><description>Recent content in Course Introduction on ModernApps Ninja New Course Template</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Docs: Tech Preview</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/techpreview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/techpreview/</guid><description>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Please Note: This course is currently in technical preview&lt;/strong> for
additional review and feedback before the course is generally available.
The purpose of the preview is to validate all information in the course
and to receive input on additions on improvements we can make before GA.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Accordingly, please be aware that any technical details in the course
are still under review and may not be fully accurate.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Your feedback is extremely important!&lt;/strong> We really need your feedback
to make this course the best experience we can. Any and all suggestions
are appreciated from small grammar improvements to bigger additions.
Please describe your suggestions with as much detail as possible. If you
would like to discuss directly with the course development team we would
appreciate it!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please &lt;a href="https://github.com/ModernAppsNinja/CourseFeedback/issues/new?assignees=&amp;amp;labels=COU-VT7933&amp;amp;template=COU-VT7933-feedback.md&amp;amp;title=">submit a feedback ticket
here&lt;/a>,
or feel free to reach out to afewell@vmware.com with other feedback or
suggestions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Welcome to the Course</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/welcometothecourse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/welcometothecourse/</guid><description>
&lt;p>This course provides a technical introduction to vSphere with Tanzu.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you complete all steps in this course, you can request a certificate
of completion, by following the instructions provided at the end of the
course. &lt;/p>
&lt;p>This course is a community effort, to be able to keep up the material,
we really need your help to report issues, suggest improvements, or help
with the many volunteer opportunities available to support the
community.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you for investing your time!&lt;/p>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5V03CSMkm2c" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Docs: Community Membership and Course Registration</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/membershipregistration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/membershipregistration/</guid><description>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#requirements-for-tests-and-course-completion-certificates">Requirements for tests and course completion certificates&lt;/a>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#join-the-modernapps-ninja-community">Join the ModernApps Ninja Community!&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#register-for-this-course">Register for this course&lt;/a>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#step-1---open-the-new-course-registration-document-link">Step 1 - Open the new course registration document link&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#step-2---name-your-file">Step 2 - Name your file&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#step-3---add-a-line-to-your-file">Step 3 - Add a line to your file&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#step-4---submit-your-registration-document">Step 4 - Submit your registration document&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="requirements-for-tests-and-course-completion-certificates">Requirements for tests and course completion certificates&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>ModernApps Ninja learning content is free and open to anyone to view, however to take tests and receive certificates of completion for courses, you must sign up for a free community membership, &lt;strong>and&lt;/strong> register for this course, per the instructions below.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="join-the-modernapps-ninja-community">Join the ModernApps Ninja Community!&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In addition to unlocking the ability to take tests and recieve course completion certificates, joining the ModernApps Ninja Community has a number of other benefits, and is a completely free program.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://modernapps.ninja/about/membership">Please click here to learn more about member benefits and to join the community!&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="register-for-this-course">Register for this course&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>You must first be a member of the community before you can register for this course. Ensure that you have fully completed the community member registration process before proceeding.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To register for this course, follow the detailed instructions below to post a simple file with your github username to this repository. This process, while simple to follow, helps participants to gain experience and comfort, and validate their knowledge with foundational devops tools and process.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Posting a file to register uses the git pull request process, which is one of the most important and common foundational skills for participating in devops, cloud native, and infrastructure modernization initiatives.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This process will also show on your public github profile that you have made a commit, the course also provides several additional exercises throughout where you will make commits to gain additional git experience while enhancing your github and professional profiles.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="step-1---open-the-new-course-registration-document-link">Step 1 - Open the new course registration document link&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>The Course Registration Process Requires that you have a github account, and that you are signed in using the github account you want to be registered for the course. If you attempt to register a different account than the account you are signed in as, the process will fail.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The following link will direct your browser to a github web-based document editor that is used to submit new files or updates to this github repository. You will need to type in a few values and then submit the document as detailed in the following steps.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please right click the following link and select the option to open it in a new browser tab, so you can keep this instruction page open in the current tab to guide you through the process.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://github.com/ModernAppsNinja/vSphereTanzu301_vt4163/tree/main/static/admin/userdata/registered_members">Right Click Here and select the option to open link in new tab&lt;/a> and click on &lt;code>Add File &amp;gt; Create new file&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="step-2---name-your-file">Step 2 - Name your file&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Note the page displays a message that &lt;code>You’re making changes in a project you don’t have write access to. Submitting a change will write it to a new branch in your fork YOUR_GITHUB_USERNAME/COURSE_REPOSITORY_NAME, so you can send a pull request.&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The pull request process works by submitting a copy of your new or updated file to the repository, which will only be applied to the course repository if a course administrator approves the request. Because you do not have write access to the repository, github will create a special copy called a &lt;code>fork&lt;/code> of the course repository within your github account with your new or updated files, and use your copy to save the updates you&amp;rsquo;re submitting to the official course repository as shown in the following steps.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In your browser tab to the new registration document, above the document editor in the file name field, type in the name of the file in the format &lt;code>your_github_username.yml&lt;/code>, replacing the value &lt;strong>your_github_username&lt;/strong> with the username for your github account.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The following screenshot shows an example of this step using the github username &lt;code>Oni-no-Hanzo&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Note:&lt;/strong> If needed, you can verify your github username by clicking on your github profile menu, which can be found on the upper right hand corner on any github page if you are signed in.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://modernapps.ninja/course_repo_template_ct8279/admin/assets/images/course_registration_file_naming.png" alt="Screenshot of File Naming">&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="step-3---add-a-line-to-your-file">Step 3 - Add a line to your file&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>On line 1 in the document editor, type &lt;code>status: in-progress&lt;/code> as shown in the following screenshot:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://modernapps.ninja/course_repo_template_ct8279/admin/assets/images/course_registration_file_editing.png" alt="Screenshot of File Editing">&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="step-4---submit-your-registration-document">Step 4 - Submit your registration document&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Scroll to the bottom of the registration document page and click &lt;code>Propose New File&lt;/code> as shown in the following image:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://github.com/ModernAppsNinja/course_repo_template_ct8279/new/main/static/admin/userdata/registered_members" alt="Propose New File Screenshot">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After you click &lt;code>Propose New File&lt;/code>, your browser will be redirected to the &lt;code>Comparing Changes&lt;/code> page with all the configuration all setup so all you sould need to do is click &lt;code>Create Pull Request&lt;/code> &amp;mdash; but before you click, please review the other details shown on the comparing changes and observe that the file you created and the lines added are shown, so you can easily review and verify your proposed changes before submitting.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After you click &lt;code>Create pull request&lt;/code>, an automated GitHub Action worklow will initiate that will do the following actions:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>verify that your github account is a member of the modernappsninja organization&lt;/li>
&lt;li>verify the filename of the submitted document matches the github username of the logged-in user that submitted the pull request&lt;/li>
&lt;li>if the above items are successfully validated:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>add the course record page to the members profile repository to display course progress and completion records&lt;/li>
&lt;li>add a message to the pull request ticket with the URL for the members course record page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>trigger github to send an email from github to the email address for the github user account that submitted the pull request including the message from the previous step&lt;/li>
&lt;li>approve and merge the new document you submitted into the registered members directory for this course&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>This completes the course registration process, once you have completed the above steps, you can proceed through the course and participate in any steps such as tests and completion certificates that require course registration.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Target Audience</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/targetaudience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/targetaudience/</guid><description>
&lt;p>This course is designed for Information Technology Professionals
interested in learning more about VMware vSphere with Tanzu.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please complete the course prerequisites and review the lab completion
difficulty to ensure you are fully prepared to succeed in this course.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Prerequisites</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/prerequisites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/prerequisites/</guid><description>
&lt;p>We recommend taking the &lt;a href="https://www.modernapps.ninja/courses/course-v1:modernapps+COU-TP6539+Perpetual/course/">Introduction to VMware Tanzu
Portfolio&lt;/a> course
prior to taking the vSphere with Tanzu 101 course. &lt;/p>
&lt;p>We also recommend completing the &lt;a href="https://www.modernapps.ninja/courses/course-v1:modernapps+COU-MN7417+Perpetual/course/">ModernApps Ninja 101
course&lt;/a> to
learn about the community resources available to support this course and
maximize your learning experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This course assumes familiarity with Kubernetes and Cloud Native
Technologies. If you are not familiar with these technologies, we
recommend checking out &lt;a href="https://kube.academy/">KubeAcademy&lt;/a> by VMware,
which has a terrific set of free, bite-size video resources on the
basics of containers, Kubernetes and cloud native that are great for
beginners.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Before taking this course, you should also have familiarity with vSphere
administration. If you need additional background in vSphere, we
recommend checking out &lt;a href="https://hol.vmware.com">VMware Hands on Labs&lt;/a>,
which offers a number of vSphere labs and content.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Course Updates and Freshness</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/courseupdatesandfreshness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/courseupdatesandfreshness/</guid><description>
&lt;p>We make a strong effort to keep the content in this course as current as
possible, however the Tanzu Portfolio is rapidly growing and there may
be times where this course may not include the newest updates. Always
please refer to the official &lt;a href="https://tanzu.vmware.com/tanzu">VMware Tanzu Portfiolio
Website&lt;/a> and your VMware account team
for the latest details on products covered in this course. &lt;/p>
&lt;p>As part of our effort to keep this course as up-to-date as possible,
this course is on a continuous update lifecycle. This means that the
course can be updated at any time, and new content and requirements may
be added while you are taking your course. We will make effort to notify
students in advance of any significant updates are made to minimize any
changes to course completion requirements. &lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Welcome to the Community</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/welcometotheninjacommunity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/welcometotheninjacommunity/</guid><description>
&lt;p>Please watch the video below to learn more about the ModernApps Ninja Community!
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GlVSmFtIs1s" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Course Input &amp; Feedback</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/coursefeedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/courseintroduction/coursefeedback/</guid><description>
&lt;p>Your feedback for this course is critical to help ensure we can improve
course content and quality and is greatly appreciated!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you see any problems or suggestions for improvement in this course, the community is very grateful for your help. The simplest way to provide your input is to click the &lt;code>Edit this page&lt;/code> link on the right nav bar on each page on this site, and it will open a page to a simple web text editor where you can easily make any update or suggested input you have and then click a button to submit your update. If the course administrators approve your update, the commit and each line you update will be shown on your public Github profile and add value to your professional portfolio, and you will be listed as a contributor to the site.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you would prefer to provide feedback through a feedback form, all feedback is crucial to helping the community provide the best content we can. If you have feedback you would rather provide through a form, please click the &amp;ldquo;Open Issue Ticket&amp;rdquo; link found on the right navigation bar on each page of this course site.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The community thanks you for your feedback and contributions!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>