<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ModernApps Ninja New Course Template – Reference Section</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference Section on ModernApps Ninja New Course Template</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 03:24:25 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Docs: How to submit tests</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/reference/testinstructions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 03:15:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/reference/testinstructions/</guid><description>
&lt;p>All Modernapps Ninja learning content is publicly accessible and available openly, however a free membership is required to take tests and recieve a certificate of completion for the course. You must first &lt;a href="https://modernapps.ninja/about/membership/">join the community&lt;/a> and register for this course per the insructions in the course introduction section before attempting to submit a test.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ninja tests use devops tools and processes so the testing system itself is educational and provides both experience and validation of foundational devops skills.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="instructions">Instructions&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Tests uses automated grading, you must follow the instructions exactly to ensure the automated grading will complete successfully.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To complete the test you must review the questions on this page, and fill in your answers on a seperate answer sheet. Each test will provide a link to the answer sheet for that test. We recommend opening the answer sheet for the test in a seperate browser tab so you can fill in the answers as you proceed through the questions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Every test question is titled &amp;ldquo;Question&amp;rdquo; followed by its order, for example Question1, Question2, Question3 etc&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>All questions will provide a list of possible answers. Each possible answer is represented by a lowercase letter, the first response is option &amp;ldquo;a&amp;rdquo;, the second is option &amp;ldquo;b&amp;rdquo; and so on, as shown in the example questions below.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Answer sheet will open in Github&amp;rsquo;s web-based editor, similar to the image shown below:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/vSphereTanzu301_vt4163/admin/assets/images/blank_test_screen_example.png" alt="Example Test Response Sheet">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After you fill in your answer sheet, you will submit your responses as a git &lt;a href="https://docs.github.com/en/github/collaborating-with-issues-and-pull-requests/about-pull-requests">pull request&lt;/a> following the instructions provided below, which will trigger a workflow that will grade your responses and provide your test grading sheet.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="example-questions">Example Questions&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Tests may contain two types of questions, multiple choice single answer, and multiple choice multiple answer, as shown in the examples below.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="example-multiple-choice-single-answer-question">Example Multiple Choice Single Answer Question&lt;/h4>
&lt;h5 id="question1-what-value-will-the-bash-shell-return-when-you-enter-the-command-echo-hello">Question1: What value will the bash shell return when you enter the command &lt;code>echo hello&lt;/code>?&lt;/h5>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>Answers:
a: banana
b: hello
c: apple
d: shutdown commencing
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;p>The correct answer to Question1 is &lt;code>b&lt;/code> as the command will return the value hello.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On your answer sheet, you would fill in the value &lt;code>b&lt;/code> for Question1, as shown in the following example:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>Question1: b
Question2:
Question3:
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;h4 id="example-multiple-choice-multiple-answer-question">Example Multiple Choice Multiple Answer Question&lt;/h4>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>Question2: Which of the following are fruits? (Select 3)
Answers:
a: banana
b: hello
c: apple
d: shutdown commencing
e: orange
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;p>&lt;strong>IMPORTANT&lt;/strong>: When providing answers to multiple choice multiple answer questions, it is important your responses are in alphabetical order. For example, the correct answer for Question2 above is &lt;code>a,c,e&lt;/code>, in alphabetical order, with a comma between each answer. If you provided the answer as &lt;code>a,e,c&lt;/code>, the grading service would mark your answer incorrect as the response values were not provided in alphabetical order.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Partially correct answers will be counted as incorrect, no partial credit is given.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You do not need to put spaces between each value in your response, but the grading service will ignore spaces if present.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On your answer sheet, you would fill in the value &lt;code>a,c,e&lt;/code> for Question2, as shown in the following example:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>Question1: b
Question2: a,c,e
Question3:
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;h3 id="submitting-your-test-response">Submitting your test response&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>After you fill in responses to all questions, scroll to the bottom of the screen and click the propose changes button as shown below:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/vSphereTanzu301_vt4163/admin/assets/images/propose_changes.png" alt="propose_new_file">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After you click propose changes:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>GitHub will automatically create a copy of the course repository on a new special copy of the repository called a &lt;strong>fork&lt;/strong> in your github account.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Your proposed changes will be saved to a &lt;a href="https://docs.github.com/en/github/collaborating-with-issues-and-pull-requests/about-branches">branch&lt;/a> on your fork of the repository.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Your browser will be directed to a screen where you can submit the updated document from your fork to the course repository&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Your browser should now show the &lt;code>Comparing Changes&lt;/code> screen, as shown in the image below:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://modernappsninja.github.io/course_repo_template_ct8279/vSphereTanzu301_vt4163/admin/assets/images/comparing_changes.png" alt="comparing_changes">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Observe that in the top part of the Comparing Changes screen:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The &lt;code>base repository&lt;/code> is the repository you are proposing changes to&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The &lt;code>head repository&lt;/code> is your fork of the repository, where the updates you have made are saved&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A directional arrow points from the head repository toward the base repository, indicating that you want the proposed update to be merged from the head, into the base repository&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>The bottom part of the Comparing Changes Screen shows the names of any files that are proposed to be updated, and displays and highlights the lines of files proposed to be changed.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Review the proposed file changes to ensure your responses look correct, and then click the &lt;code>Create pull request&lt;/code> button.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="reviewing-your-test-response">Reviewing your test response&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>After you click the &lt;code>Create pull request&lt;/code> button, you will be directed to a new page where you can review the status of your pull request.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the same time, an automated github actions workflow will evaluate your test responses, post a test grading report to your member repo, and post a message alerting you with the link to your report. The link to your file will be similar to the following, with the values for your username and the course repository name for the test you are taking: &lt;code>https://github.com/modernappsninjas/YOUR_GITHUB_USERNAME/static/admin/userdata/COURSE_REPO_NAME/testresults&lt;/code>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you passed the test, it will also be indicated on the course record card on your member and a message will be sent to you with the link to your record card for the course. The link to your file will be similar to the following, with the values for your username and the course repository name for the test you are taking: &lt;code>https://github.com/modernappsninjas/YOUR_GITHUB_USERNAME/content/english/course/COURSE_REPO_NAME.md&lt;/code>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Your course record card will display each test in the course, and if that test has been completed, for example:&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre style="background-color:#f8f8f8;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4">&lt;code class="language-yml" data-lang="yml">&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">Tests&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">Test1&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Completed Successfully&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">Test2&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Pending&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">Test3&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Pending&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div>&lt;p>If you do not pass the test, the course record card is not modified, and the result will only be reflected on the test grading report.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This complete the instructions for taking tests. If you have additional questions, please search the member discussion board and issue ticket records at &lt;a href="https://github.com/modernappsninja/modernappsninja.github.io">https://github.com/modernappsninja/modernappsninja.github.io&lt;/a> and if you cannot find an answer to your question, please open an issue ticket on this course repository. Thank you!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>